{
    "id": "ea7718b41380412a891e05b0d3865d01",
    "title": "All vs. Every",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "21ceb77ea4fa43568809b751bc294c0a",
            "title": "All vs. Every",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I  visit him .................................. other day.",
                    "description": "Use every with singular noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Buses leave ..................................... 15 minutes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "all"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I answered ........................................ the questions.",
                    "description": "All is used with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was working ................................ day yesterday.",
                    "description": "All day means from morning to evening.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She drank ................................... the water in the bottle.",
                    "description": "Either all or all of is possible here.  All is used with plural and uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every",
                        "all of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has invited ................................... of you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. my family live in different parts of India.",
                    "description": "Before a noun with a determiner, all and all of are both possible.",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "Everyone",
                        "All of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was crying ..................................... the way.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She lost .......................................... in the war.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "everything"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She lost ..................................... that she owned in the disaster.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ I want is something to eat and drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "Everything"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. stood up.",
                    "description": "All does not normally mean everybody.",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "Everybody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}